http://www.digicardservices.com/privacy

Call Toll Free: 866-916-5100
Free Shipping on Orders over $100* ($3.00 Handling Fee)
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the DigiCard Services website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive material. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
. Name
. Address
. Email Address
. Phone Number
. Credit/Debit Card Information
. (etc)
On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient’s address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are:
. Name
. Address
. Email Address
. Phone Number
. (etc)
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
We use return email address to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain inormation at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Acces Or Correct Your Information
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How To Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1516-432-5002 or send us an email at info@weneedbadges.com.
My Account
Returns/Exchanges
Shipping
Contact
© 2017 Digicard Service Group, Inc. - All Rights Reserved.
Got Questions ? Call us 24/7!
(866) 916-5100
